Guide to the Tristan Taormino papers, 1989-2014.
Taormino, Tristan papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Tristan Taormino papers, 1989-2014.
7819
Taormino, Tristan,
12.3 cubic feet, 4 mapcase folders
Audio recordings, correspondence, legal documents, manuscripts, memorabilia, photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Books, articles, and movies Taormino wrote and directed, along with drafts, correspondence about their creation, production books for the movies and couple plays she directed, promotional material, and reviews and media coverage. There are audio and visual recordings of her lectures and media appearances. From her undergraduate years at Wesleyan, there are papers written for classes and her senior thesis, plus ephemera from sexuality activism. Also included is Taormino's collection of ephemera, posters, booklets, zines, magazines, and books written, produced, and created by other people on the topics of sex, sex positivity, gender LGBT/queer issues, BDSM, kink, leather, polyamory and non-monogamy, erotica and erotic photography, and pornography and feminist porn.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
A sex educator and feminist pornographer, Tristan has authored and edited numerous books and anthologies, which have sold over 500,000 copies and been translated into multiple languages. Early in her career, she worked as the Executive Assistant to Jay Hill, the Executive Director of the Gay Games (1994). Her first prominent job in erotic and feminist publishing came when she served first as columnist, then as editor of the feminist sex magazine On Our Backs (1998-2002). For nine and a half years (1999-2008), she wrote a bi-weekly column in The Village Voice, which appeared alongside Dan Savage's column "Savage Love" and won two Sex-Positive Journalism Awards. She wrote an advice column for Hustler's Taboo Magazine from 1999-2014. Her articles have appeared in Penthouse, Yale Journal of Law and Feminism, and numerous other publications. She runs her own adult film production company, Smart Ass Productions, started in 2005, and she was an exclusive director for Vivid Entertainment from 2006-2012, where she created and helmed the Vivid-Ed sex education line. She has directed and produced 25 adult films which have won numerous awards, including her multi-award winning debut film based on her book, The Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women (1998). She has appeared on dozens of television shows alongside Ricki Lake, Melissa Harris-Perry, Howard Stern, and others; she worked as a script consultant for Spike Lee and appeared in John Cameron Mitchell's film Shortbus. She has lectured and taught workshops extensively throughout the United States, Canada, Germany, Sweden, Spain, and Australia at colleges, universities, conferences, and community events. She has been producer and host of the radio show and podcast Sex Out Loud since 2012.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes books, articles, and movies which Taormino wrote and directed, along with drafts, correspondence about their creation, production books for the movies and plays she directed, final commercial versions, and rough cut footage, as well as promotional material, reviews, and media coverage. There are audio and visual recordings of her lectures and appearances on television and radio. From her undergraduate years at Wesleyan University, there are papers written for classes and her senior thesis, plus ephemera from sexuality activism. Also included is Taormino's collection of ephemera, conference materials, posters, booklets, zines, magazines, and books written, produced, and created by other people on the topics of sex, sex positivity, gender LGBT/queer issues, BDSM, kink, leather, polyamory and non-monogamy, erotica and erotic photography, and pornography and feminist porn. There are also materials related to her work as an LGBT consultant for Spike Lee's film She Hate Me.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Taormino, Tristan, 1971-
Subjects:
Sex.; Homosexuality.; Non-monogamous relationships.; Anal sex.; Erotica.; Photography, Erotic.; Pornography.; Bondage (Sexual behavior); Sadomasochism.
Form and Genre Terms:
Video recordings.; Ephemera (general); Posters.; Fanzines.; Zines.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Box 2 Folder 25 is restricted until 2055.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Wesleyan University Years
Box 1
Series II. Gay Games IV & Cultural Festival Materials
Boxes 1, 18
Series III. Publications
Boxes 2-7, 10-14, 18-20
Articles
Village Voice
Outlook Weekly
Hustler's Taboo
Freelance Writing & Syndication
Reviews & Interviews of Taormino's Work
Books, Magazines, & Related Materials
The Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women
Pucker Up: A Hands-on Guide to Ecstatic Sex
Opening Up
Pucker Up Magazine
Best Lesbian Erotica
Conference Materials
Promotional Materials
Series IV. Public Appearances & Related Materials
Boxes 2, 8, 12, 19
Workshops & Lectures
Radio
Television
The Ricki Lake Show
Other Appearances
Series V. Projects
Boxes 9-10, 12, 14-17, 20
Smart Ass Productions
Final Versions/Commercial Copies
Rough Footage
Other Films
She Hate Me
Dark Odyssey
Series VI. Correspondence
Boxes 12, 19
Fan Mail
Anal Advisor
Series VII. Assorted Materials
Boxes 1, 7-8, 12, 18-19
Separated Materials
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Wesleyan University Years
  - Look for the Lights, 1986-1989; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Play Taormino wrote and directed in high school, based on a story by Gabrielle Maloney
  - Wesleyan University miscellaneous, 1988-04-11-1994-05 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes correspondence regarding LGBT studies course proposal, scholarship award letters, photo of Wesleyan campus, Phi Beta Kappa materials, course syllabi, applications, general correspondence, GLAAD internship materials, Report of A.S.A.P.: The Assessment of Sexual Abuse Policies Task Force, Wesleyan University commencement program
    Wesleyan University; Middletown, Connecticut
  - Clippings of interest, 1988-09-1994-10, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Includes article clippings and book excerpts
  - "Revolutionary Clitoris" flyer, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Flyer for a party at her special interest campus housing, Womanist House
  - Student papers, 1989-1993; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Paper topics include Comedy and Christianity Center Around a Courtesan: a comparison of The Eunuch and Paphntius; Allegory in Early European Drama: a matter of life and death - A comparison of English morality plays and Spanish autos sacrametales with Everyman and La Vida es Sueňo as Representative work; Consumerism and Its Link to Happiness: a comparison between Paul's Case and Sister Carrie; Crossing the Color Line or Straddling It?: a comparison of Leaves from the Mental Portfolio of a Eurasian and The Autobiography of an Ex-Colored Man
  - Student papers, 1989-1993; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Includes papers on Madonna and the Making of a Lesbian, Joe Turner's Come and Gone, and The Singular Life of Albert Nobbs
  - Madonna: The Lesbian Icon video, 1991-12; V-9759; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1)
    Video supplement to her college paper on "Madonna: Lesbian Icon"
  - "Attractions" production binder, 1990-09-1991-02; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1)
    Binder for play directed by Taormino. Sections include production book; design book; and budget/miscellaneous; as well as show assignments, folder of publicity materials, schedules
  - "Attractions" video, 1991-02; V-9758 (Box 1)
    Recording of the play "Attractions" she directed in college
  - Thesis meeting notes notebook, 1991-1992; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1)
  - Queer activism, 1991-1994-10-10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes 5th annual Lesbian and Gay Studies Conference packet, BDSM in NYC handouts, first edition of the Purple Circuit Newsletter, newspaper and magazine clippings, Buttons and Bumper Stickers order form, 9th annual Los Angeles International Gay and Lesbian Film and Video Festival calendar, Astraea National Lesbian Action Foundation Bulletin
  - Senior thesis, 1991-1993-05-30 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Includes notes on thesis and invitation to Class of 1993 commencement ceremony
  - Wesleyan papers, 1991-09-17-1993-05-05; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Paper topics include Queer Nerd Fantasies: Theory, Politics, and Making a Difference in the Academy; A Parody of the Straight Mind: The Subversion of Hegemonic Discourse of Gender and Sexuality in Kiss of the Spiderwoman; The Possession and Obsession of the Phallic Source: Gender, Hetero/Sexuality, and Alternative Sources of Pleasure in D.H. Lawrence's Women in Love; Lesbians and Political Identity: Issues of Separatism in the Gay and Lesbian Community; Tie Me Up and Set My Body Free or Macho Sluts Coming to Power: Audre Lorde's "Uses of the Erotic" and Lesbian Sadomasochism; Women's Studies final exam; Renegotiating Parenthood: Inventing the Male Mother in the Baby M Case
  - B/F interviews journal, 1992; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1)
  - Paper notes notebook, 1992; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1)
  - Poster campaign, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Posters put up during orientation, not by the official LGBT group, created controversy because of sexually explicit language
  - SOC 224: Lesbian/Bisexual/Gay People in Society, 1992-09-1992-12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Taormino helped design this course, one of the first LGBT Studies courses, and served as a Teaching Assistant; includes course syllabus, photocopied readings
  - Law school materials, 1992-11-1994-01 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Includes correspondence with schools and application materials
  - Iahu feminist journal, 1992-12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    First publication of journal; Tristan Taormino listed as contributor; 2 copies
  - Dressing Up and Fleshing Out: Butch/Femme Erotics and Politics All Tied Up, 1993-04; Taormino, Tristan (Box 1)
    Thesis submitted by Taormino under advisor Claire Potter
  - Pilgrims of the Night, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Materials related to a New City play Taormino worked as a production intern on
- Series II. Gay Games IV & Cultural Festival Materials
  - Gay Games IV folder, 1987-07-27, 1992-04-14-1994-06-28 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Includes photocopied articles, correspondence, promotional materials, athlete registration book and materials, other games and festival materials
  - Gay Games IV assorted materials, 1993-07-29-1994-06-28 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Includes photocopied articles, correspondence, promotional materials, copies of message from the White House, advertising packets
  - Gay Games IV & Cultural Festival binder materials, 1994-06-16-1994-06-29 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Taormino worked as Executive Assistant to Jay Hill, the Executive Director of the Gay Games. Formerly housed in binder. Sections include Itinerary; Cultural Festival; Donors; Hotel; Opening/Closing, PR, Security; Other Events; Receptions; Sports; Staff
  - LGBT programs, 1994-06-16-1994-06-29 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Includes programs for Gay Games IV & Cultural Festival, Stonewall 25, and Outrageous Comedy '94
  - Village Voice article on the Gay Games, 1994-12-20-1994-12-27 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gay Games IV & Cultural Festival buttons & pins, 1994; MU-1781-1786 (Box 18)
- Series III. Publications
  - Articles
    - Village Voice
      - Village Voice materials, 1999-07-2008-07 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Pucker Up column, 1999-08-2003-05; Taormino, Tristan (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Pucker Up column, 1999-08-24-1999-12-28; Taormino, Tristan (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Pucker Up column, 1999-12-2006-03; Taormino, Tristan (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Pucker Up column, 2000-01-11-2000-05-30; Taormino, Tristan (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Pucker Up column, 2000-06-13-2000-10-31; Taormino, Tristan (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Pucker Up column, 2000-11-14-2001-03-21; Taormino, Tristan (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Pucker Up column, 2001-04-03-2001-08-21; Taormino, Tristan (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Pucker Up column, 2001-09-04-2001-12-25; Taormino, Tristan (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Pucker Up column, 2002-01-08-2002-06-25; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Pucker Up column, 2002-07-16-2002-12-24; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Pucker Up column, 2003-01-01-2003-05-27; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Pucker Up column, 2003-06-04-2003-11-11; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Pucker Up column, 2003-11-19-2004-03-30; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Pucker Up column, 2004-04-07-2004-08-03; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Pucker Up column, 2004-08-11-2005-03-15; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Pucker Up column, 2005-04-20-2006-03-28; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Pucker Up column, 2006-06-14-2008-01-22; Taormino, Tristan (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Outlook Weekly
      - Pucker Up column, 2004-07-29-2004-12-29; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Pucker Up column, 2004-12-30-2005-05-18; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Pucker Up column, 2005-05-26-2005-10-19; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Pucker Up column, 2005-10-27-2006-03-22; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Pucker Up column, 2006-03-30-2006-08-30; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Pucker Up column, 2006-09-07-2007-04-11; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Pucker Up column, 2007-04-19-2007-10-03; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Pucker Up column, 2007-10-11-2008-02-13; Taormino, Tristan (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Hustler's Taboo
      - Anal Advisor column, 1998-2014; Taormino, Tristan (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Anal Advisor column, 1998-2014; Taormino, Tristan (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Anal Advisor column, 1998-2014; Taormino, Tristan (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Freelance Writing & Syndication
      - Spectator articles, Undated; Taormino, Tristan (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Assorted publications, 1994-11-1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
        Includes Masquerade Erotic Newsletter, Venus Infers, Blue Blood, Purr
      - Press Clips - Freelance Writing, 1995-2005; Taormino, Tristan (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Press Clips - Freelance Writing, 1995-2005; Taormino, Tristan (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Assorted publications, 1995-01-1997-08-19 (Box 10, Folder 4)
        Includes On Our Backs, Live Girls, Icon, Plazm, and The Advocate
      - Assorted publications, 1996-11-1997-08; Taormino, Tristan (Box 6, Folder 4)
        Includes Sojourner Vol. 22 No. 3 and The Lesbian Review of Books Vol. III No. 4
      - Assorted publications, 1997-08-25-1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
        Includes New York Magazine, Entertainment Weekly On Campus, Out, Ben is Dead
      - On Our Backs materials, 1998-01-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
        Includes photographs, correspondence, contract
      - Assorted publications, 1998-04-1999-01 (Box 10, Folder 7)
        Includes Paper, Playboy, On Our Backs
      - Assorted publications, 1999-05-2001-07 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        Includes Curve, XXX Movie Illustrated, Out, Redbook, Hustler's Taboo
      - Assorted Village Voice articles, 1999-08-10-2002-10-08; Taormino, Tristan (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Loop articles, 2000-01-2001-03; Taormino, Tristan (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Assorted publications, 2002-01-22-2004-08 (Box 10, Folder 9)
        Includes The Advocate, Girlfriends, Playboy, Playgirl, L Mag, Print
      - Assorted publications, 2007-07- 2009-02 (Box 10, Folder 10)
        Includes Oprah Magazine, HQ Trade Magazine, Storerotica
      - Assorted publications, 2011-09-2012-02 (Box 10, Folder 11)
        Includes Fox, Velvet, and Inked
  - Reviews & Interviews of Taormino's Work
    - Press Clips - Pucker Up/Down and Dirty, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Press Clips - College Lectures, 2001-2011 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Press Clips - House of Ass, 2005-2006-05 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Press Clips - True Lust, 2002-2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Press Clips - Best Lesbian Erotica, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Best Lesbian Erotica: Reviews, 1996-04-1997-05 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Press Clips - Best Lesbian Erotica, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Press Clips - Best Lesbian Erotica, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Press Clips - Best Lesbian Erotica, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Press Clips - Best Lesbian Erotica, 2000-01-2008-01 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Press Clips - Ritual Sex, 1996-08-2004-06 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Press Clips - Smart Ass Productions, 2006-2007-12 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Chemistry film series
    - Press Clips - Smart Ass Productions, 2006-04-2009-06 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      General
    - Press Clips - Smart Ass Productions, 2007-2009 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Top Charts
    - Press Clips - Smart Ass Productions, 2007-07-2009-01 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Vivid Education films
    - Press Clips - Smart Ass Productions, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Rough Sex films
    - Press Clips - General Profiles, 2005-04-2011-10 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Press Clips - General Profiles, 1997-08-2006-04 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Press Clips - General Profiles, 1997-08-2002-11 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Press Clips - Books, 1997-11-2008-12 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Sections include Fem Porn, UGT Kink, Take Me There, G-Spot, Sex Toys, ASPG, Opening Up
    - Press Clips - Zine Book, 1994-12-1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Pucker Up section
    - Press Clips - Zine Book, 1997-03-2003-02 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Writing section
    - Press Clips - Zine Book, 1997-04-1999-12 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      A Girl's Guide to Taking Over the World
    - Press Clips - Ultimate Guide, 1997-2007-11 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Press Clips - Ultimate Guide, 1998-03-2003-03 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Press Clips - Spike Lee, 2004-06-2004-08 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      Articles on Spike Lee's movie She Hate Me on which Taormino served as a consultant
    - Assorted reviews, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Includes The Village Voice, The Triad, Just Out, L Mag, Greater Greensboro Observer. New York Blade, The Advocate, The Carolinian
    - Assorted reviews, 2005-04 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Includes The New Haven Advocate, Teu, The Brown Daily Hearld, Bay Windows Arts
    - Assorted reviews, 2006-02-22-2006-05-16 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Includes New York Press, City Beat
    - Assorted reviews, 2007-02-2007-07 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Includes Philadelphia City Paper, Xbiz Video, Oprah Magazine
    - Assorted reviews, 2008-03-2008-09 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Includes The Window, Just Out, Ann Novelty Business
    - Assorted reviews, 2009-11-05-2009-11-11 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Includes Weekly Alibi
    - Assorted reviews, 2010-02-2010-04 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Includes The Stranger, Willamette, Eye Weekly
    - Assorted reviews, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Includes The Sunday Age, Cherrie, In terrobang
    - Tales of a Butt Bandit, Undated (Mapcase-folder 3)
      Mounted and framed pages from a magazine profile of Tristan Taormino
  - Books, Magazines, & Related Materials
    - The Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Galleys, 1998; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 1)
        Photocopy of The Ultimate Guide to Anal Sex for Women with notes
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Drafts, 1997; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Includes early drafts, correspondence, and handwritten notes
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Readings, Events, Tour, 1997-05-28-1998-02-11; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 3)
        Includes correspondence and book tour information
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Research, 1997-07-31-1997-09-23; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 4)
        Includes correspondence, information for books consulted, photocopied excerpts, notes
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Backdoor Betty Party NYC, 1997-07-16-1999-06-23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        Includes event related materials, such as promotional material and talking points
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Miscellaneous, 1997-09-22-1999-08-11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        Includes correspondence, promotional material, contract drafts, notes
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Resource Guide, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Ultimate Guide 1st Edition: Surveys, 1997-05-06-1997-07-16 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Includes email responses to survey on anal sex
      - Draft Manuscript for 2nd Edition - 1, 2004-2006; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Includes manuscript with notes and in-line edits
      - Draft Manuscript for 2nd Edition - 2, 2004-2006; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Draft Manuscript for 2nd Edition -3, 2004-2006; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Includes manuscript, notes, research
      - Anal Sex book launch party photo board, 1998-01 (Box 7, Folder 3)
        Book launch party in NYC for Anal Sex, photo including Carmelita Tropicana
    - Pucker Up: A Hands-on Guide to Ecstatic Sex
      - New Book: Art, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - New Book: Editor, 2000-10-23 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        Includes correspondence with editor suggestions
      - New Book: Research, 1996-12-2000-09 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        Includes articles, correspondence, printed webpages
      - New Book: Events, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Includes guest list
      - New Book: Miscellaneous, 2000-05-2001-12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        Includes Pucker Up press release, printed web searches, book tour travel expense
      - New Book: Publicity, 2001-06-2001-11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        Includes list of media contacts, correspondence, interviews, book reviews
      - New Book: Proposal, 2000-05; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Pucker Up manuscript, 2001-05; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 19)
        Includes handwritten notes
      - Pucker Up manuscript, 2001-06; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Pucker Up poster board, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Opening Up
      - Surveys, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        Access restrictions apply.
        Restricted until 2055
      - Research, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        Includes articles, notes, magazines, printed webpages and photocopied excerpts
      - The Ultimate Guide to Non-Monogamy for Couples, 2003-2007; Wilde, Winston; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2)
      - Opening Up draft, 2003-2007; Taormino, Tristan (Box 2, Folder 22)
        Includes notes and manuscript with annotations
      - OU Interviews: Amber, 2004-2005; CD-3399 (Box 20)
        Disk 1
      - OU Interviews: Adrine, 2004-2005; CD-3400 (Box 20)
        Disk 2
      - OU Interviews: Bobby, 2004-2005; CD-3401 (Box 20)
        Disk 3
      - OU Interviews: Chuck, Jamie, 2004-2005; CD-3402 (Box 20)
        Disk 4
      - OU Interviews: Rebecca Pony / Lee MC, 2004-2005; CD-3403 (Box 20)
        Disk 5
      - OU Interviews: Jen B + Liz, 2004-2005; CD-3404 (Box 20)
        Disk 6
      - OU Interviews: Madeline, Maka / Cat, Naima, 2004-2005; CD-3405 (Box 20)
        Disk 7
      - OU Interviews: Sarah L / Sean Michael, 2004-2005; CD-3406 (Box 20)
        Disk 8
      - OU Interviews: Aaron, Amy, Megan, 2004-2005; CD-3407 (Box 20)
        Disk 9
      - OU Interviews: Dave H, Jon W, 2004-2005; CD-3408 (Box 20)
        Disk 10
      - OU Interviews: Rebecca + Tom Z, 2004-2005; CD-3409 (Box 20)
        Disk 11
      - OU Interviews: Barb + Dylan, Clyde, 2004-2005; CD-3410 (Box 20)
        Disk 12
      - OU Interviews: Mark + Patricia, 2004-2005; CD-3411 (Box 20)
        Disk 13
      - OU Interviews: Rebecca, 2004-2005; CD-3412 (Box 20)
        Disk 14
      - OU Interviews: Reid + Marcia, 2004-2005; CD-3413 (Box 20)
        Disk 15
      - OU Interviews: Anton, Melanie, 2004-2005; CD-3414 (Box 20)
        Disk 16
      - OU Interviews: Ignacio + Khane, Rick, 2004-2005; CD-3415 (Box 20)
        Disk 17
      - OU Interviews: Jon W, 2004-2005; CD-3416 (Box 20)
        Disk 18
      - OU Interviews: Brian B + Claudia, 2004-2005; CD-3417 (Box 20)
        Disk 19